Finding Aid for Gerald L. K. Smith Papers 1922-1976
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Chronological files
  - 1947
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Perkins, J. E. (Box 22)
    - Peyton, Rupert (Box 22)
    - Philadelphia meeting (Box 22)
    - Phoenix meeting (Box 22)
    - Press releases (Box 22)
    - Q-R (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Reilly, Lawrence (Box 22)
      (director, Lutheran Research Society)
    - Robertson, Charles and B. N. (Box 22)
    - Russian Embassy (Box 22)
      (picketing incident and subsequent indictment)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Sadowski, Harold (Box 22)
      (attorney)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 22)
    - Saint Louis meetings (Box 22)
    - Schickedanz, Forrest (Box 22)
    - Shepler, Charles (Box 22)
    - Shreveport (La.) meeting (Box 22)
    - Smith, Gerald, Jr. (Box 22)
    - Smith, L. Z. (Box 22)
      (Smith's parents)
    - Springer, Harvey (Box 22)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Tanner, Opal (Box 22)
    - Terminello, Rev. Arthur (Box 22)
    - Tulsa meetings (Box 22)
    - U-V (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Washington meeting (Box 22)
    - Winnfield (La.) meeting (Box 22)
    - Winrod, Gerald P. (Box 22)
    - X-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
  - 1948
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Advertising, clippings (Box 22)
    - Appeals (form letters) (Box 22)
    - Armstrong, George W. (Box 22)
    - Armstrong, Judge, Foundation (Box 22)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 23)
    - Birmingham (Ala.) Trip - pledges (Box 23)
    - Burke, Emory (Box 23)
    - Byrth, T. Joseph (Box 23)
      (St. Louis attorney)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Christian Nationalist Crusade record of checks and money orders (Box 23)
    - Christian Nationalist Party convention (Box 23)
    - Circulars (Box 23)
    - Columbia Press (Box 23)
    - Commercial Publishers (Box 23)
    - Committee for the Investigation of Un-American Activities (Box 23)
    - Congressional Endorsements (Box 23)
    - Consolidated Press Clipping Bureau (Box 23)
    - Cross and the Flag (Box 23)
    - Cross and the Flag record of checks and money orders (Box 23)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Denver meetings (Box 23)
    - Dewey, Thomas (Box 23)
    - Doman, Bernard A. (Box 23)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Elmhurst, Ernest (Box 23)
    - Emergency (appeal) letters (Box 23)
    - Expiration letters (Box 23)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 23)
    - Ferguson, Homer (Box 23)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - "Gentleman’s Agreement" law suit (Box 23)
    - Goff, Kenneth (Box 23)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Hall, Gordon (Box 23)
    - Hamilton, John (Box 23)
    - Heal, H. J. (Box 23)
      (Mrs. Smith's sister's family)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Jaques, Norman (Box 24)
    - Jones, Ellis O. (Box 24)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Kamp, Joseph P. (Box 24)
    - Kerr, Robert (Box 24)
    - Kister, Fred (Box 24)
      (Christian Veterans Political Council)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Lane Memo (Box 24)
    - Latimer, J. Austin (Box 24)
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 24)
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 24)
      (checks and money orders received as agent)
    - Los Angeles meeting (Box 24)
    - Luther, Martin (Box 24)
      ("The Jews and their Lies")
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - McAllister, Andrew B. (Box 24)
    - McFarland, W. Henry (Box 24)
    - Mannery, E. E., printer (Box 24)
    - Mannery Printing Co. (Box 24)
    - Marion, Leland L. (Box 24)
    - Memos, 7 folders (Box 24)
    - Midwestern Political Survey Institute record of checks and money orders (Box 24)
    - Minneapolis meeting (Box 24)
    - Moseley, George Van Horn (Box 25)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Newsletters (Box 25)
      (The Letter)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Oklahoma States Rights League (Box 25)
    - Open letter to Congress (Box 25)
    - Open letter to Senate (Box 25)
    - Operatives (Box 25)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Perkins, Jonathan E. (Box 25)
    - Perkins, Jonathan E., agent (Box 25)
      (record of checks and money orders)
    - Perkins, M. L. (Box 25)
      (Mrs. Jonathan E. Perkins)
    - Press releases (Box 25)
    - Preston, Jack (Box 25)
    - Protocols of the Elders of Zion (Box 25)
    - Public Letter Shop (Box 25)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Reilly, Lawrence (Box 25)
      (The Eleventh Hour)
    - Reports to Congress (Box 25)
    - Response Letters (Box 25)
    - Russian Embassy (Box 25)
      (Lohbeck trial)
    - S miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 25)
    - St. Louis meetings (Box 25)
    - Sampson, James O. (Box 25)
      (St. Louis landlord)
    - Schickendanz, Forrest (Box 25)
    - Smith, Gerald, Jr. (Box 25)
    - Smith, Gomer, Sr. (Box 25)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Z. (Box 25)
    - Special letters and lists (Box 25)
    - Springer, Harvey (Box 25)
    - Swift, Wesley (Box 25)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Tanner, Opal (Box 25)
    - Tracts, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Tulsa meetings (Box 25)
    - U-V (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Washington Letters (Box 25)
    - Winrod, Gerald B. (Box 25)
    - Winrod, Gerald B (about) (Box 26)
    - Wise, James E. (Box 26)
    - X (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
    - [Mr.] X manuscript (Box 26)
    - Y-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
  - 1949
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
    - Advertising (Box 26)
    - Alameda case (Box 26)
    - Allstorm, Oliver (Box 26)
    - Allstorm, Oliver (Box 26)
      (poetry)
    - Alworth, G. N. (Box 26)
    - Antiques (Box 26)
    - Appeal letters (Box 26)
    - Armstrong, George W. (Box 26)
    - Armstrong Foundation (Box 26)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
    - Broenstrup, H. V. (Box 26)
    - Burke, Emory (Box 26)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
    - California meetings (Box 26)
    - Chicago Defense Funds (Box 26)
    - Christian Nationalist Convention, 4 folders (Box 26)
    - Commercial Publishers (Box 26)
    - Committee for the Investigation of Un-American Activities (Box 26)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
    - Davis, Phil W. (Jr.) (Box 26)
    - Denver meetings (Box 26)
    - Dilling law suit (Box 26)
    - Dog data (Box 26)
    - Doman, Bernard A. - printing orders (Box 26)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 26)
    - Elmhurst, Ernest F. (Box 26)
    - El Paso meeting (Box 26)
    - Estill, P. E. (Box 27)
    - Expiration Letters (Box 27)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 27)
    - Fagan, Myron C. (Box 27)
      (Cinema Educational Guild)
    - Fagan manuscript: "Communism in Hollywood" (Box 27)
    - Federation of Americanization of Michigan (Box 27)
    - First Christian Church, Tulsa, Oklahoma (Box 27)
    - Foreign correspondence (Box 27)
    - Franklin, Benjamin and the Jews (Box 27)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 27)
    - Gibbons, Russell (Box 27)
    - Goad, Daisy (Box 27)
      (staff of Senator Elmer Thomas)
    - Goff, Kenneth (Box 27)
    - Green, G. F. (Box 27)
      (editor of Independent Nationalist, England)
    - Ha-Hd (miscellaneous) (Box 27)
    - He-Hz (miscellaneous) (Box 27)
    - Hamilton, John W.
      - Personal (Box 27)
      - Order department (Box 27)
    - Inventory of publications (Box 27)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 27)
    - Jaques, Norman (Box 27)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 27)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 27)
    - LaCroix, Florence (Box 27)
    - Loans (Box 27)
    - Lohbeck, Donald (Box 27)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 27)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 27)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 28)
    - MacFarland, W. Henry, Jr. (Box 28)
    - Manney, E. E. - printer (Box 28)
    - Marion, Leland L. (Box 28)
    - Memos
      - Jan.-Apr. (Box 28)
      - May-Aug. (Box 28)
      - Sept.-Dec. (Box 28)
    - Menjou, Adolph (Box 28)
      (testimony before House Un-American Activities Committee)
    - Moragon, John (Box 28)
      (informant)
    - Moseley, George Van Horn (Box 28)
    - Murray, William H. (Box 28)
      (Governor of Oklahoma)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 28)
    - Newsletters (Box 28)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 28)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 28)
    - Pearson, Drew - Smith brochures about (Box 28)
    - Perkins, Jonathan (Box 28)
    - Petitions (Box 28)
    - Pollock, Clara (Box 28)
    - Press releases (Box 28)
    - Preston, Jack (Box 28)
    - Price lists for literature (Box 28)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 28)
    - Race Purity League (Box 28)
    - Rankin, John E. (Box 28)
      (U. S. Congress)
    - Response form letters (Box 28)
    - Sa-Sl (miscellaneous) (Box 28)
    - Si-So (miscellaneous) (Box 28)
    - Sp-Sz (miscellaneous) (Box 28)
    - Sadowski, Harold (Box 28)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 28)
    - St. Louis meetings (Box 28)
    - Singeltary, H. A. (Box 28)
    - Smith, Gerald L. K. (Box 28)
      (re income tax)
    - Smith, Gerry, Jr. (Box 29)
    - Smith, Gomer (Box 29)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Z. (Box 29)
    - Special form letters (Box 29)
    - Suicide manuscript (Box 29)
    - Swift, Wesley (Box 29)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 29)
    - Tanner, Opal M. (Box 29)
    - Telephone numbers and addresses (Box 29)
    - Terminiello, Arthur (Box 29)
      (appeal to U. S. Supreme Court)
    - Tracts (Box 29)
    - Tulsa meetings (Box 29)
    - Twentieth Century Tax (Box 29)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 29)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 29)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 29)
    - Washington newsletters (Box 29)
    - Welch, James (Box 29)
    - Xavier, Peter L. (Box 29)
    - Y-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 29)
  - 1950
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 29)
    - Advertising newspapers (Box 29)
    - Allen, Marilyn R. (Box 29)
    - Allstorm, Oliver (Box 29)
    - Anti-Communist League (Box 29)
    - Appeal form letters, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Appeal letters - drafts and related, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Armstrong, George W. (Box 29)
    - Attack (Box 29)
      (periodical edited by Don Lohbeck)
    - Ba-Bn (miscellaneous) (Box 29)
    - Bo-Bz (miscellaneous) (Box 29)
    - Burke, Emory (Box 29)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 30)
    - Cartoonists (Box 30)
    - Cash (Box 30)
    - Cawthorn, Joe T. (Box 30)
    - Chicago Tribune (Box 30)
      (re article on secret "Jewish" government)
    - Christian Herald (Box 30)
      (article re GLKS and related correspondence)
    - Christian Nationalist Convention, Los Angeles, July 20-23 (Box 30)
    - Christian Nationalist Party (Box 30)
    - Circulars (Box 30)
    - Commercial Publishers (Box 30)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 30)
    - Denver meeting (Box 30)
    - Doman, Bernard, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 30)
    - Elmhurst, Ernest (Box 30)
    - Estill, Paul (Box 30)
    - Expiration Letter (Box 30)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 30)
    - Foreign correspondence, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 30)
    - Goodyear, Steve (Box 30)
    - Green, G. F. (Box 30)
    - Ha (miscellaneous) (Box 30)
    - He-Hz (miscellaneous) (Box 30)
    - Hamilton, John W. (Box 31)
      (orders and correspondence)
    - Harris, Louva M. (Box 31)
    - Hart, Merwin K. (Box 31)
    - Heal, H. J. (Box 31)
    - Heller, Samuel, lawsuit (Box 31)
    - Howard, M. W. (Box 31)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 31)
    - Income Tax (Box 31)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 31)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 31)
    - Kamp, Joseph P. (Box 31)
    - Kaub, Verne P. (Box 31)
    - Kister, Frederick (Box 31)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 31)
    - Legant, Renata (Box 31)
    - Levine, Isaac (Box 31)
    - Literature Purchasers (Box 31)
    - Loans (Box 31)
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles meetings
      - General (Box 31)
      - Jan.-Mar. (including some Dec. 1949) (Box 31)
      - June-Sept., 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Ma-Mn (miscellaneous) (Box 31)
    - Mo-Mz (miscellaneous) (Box 31)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 31)
    - McCarthy, Joseph (Box 31)
    - Manney, E. E. (Box 31)
    - Memos, 4 folders (Box 32)
    - Morris, Emmett (Box 32)
    - Moseley, George Van Horn (Box 32)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 32)
    - New Orleans Item (Box 32)
    - Newsletters (Box 32)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 32)
    - North, George (Box 32)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 32)
    - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, meeting (Box 32)
    - Oklahoma Public School Defence League (Box 32)
    - Orders - filled (Box 32)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 32)
    - Pelley, William Dudley (Box 32)
    - Pollock, Clara (Box 32)
    - Press releases (Box 32)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 32)
    - Radio broadcasts, 2 folders (Box 32)
      (Missouri campaigns of Don Lohbeck and John Hamilton)
    - Response letters (Box 32)
    - Ring, William C. (Box 32)
    - Robertson, Charles (Box 32)
      (Robertson Printing Co.)
    - Rosenberg, Anna
      (confirmation as assistant secretary of defense)
      - Correspondence (Box 32)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 32)
      - Government documents and periodicals (Box 32)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 32)
    - Sadowski, Harold (Box 33)
    - Saint Louis meetings (Box 33)
    - Salt Lake City (Box 33)
    - Sammons, F. C. (Box 33)
    - Schlather, C. C. (Box 33)
    - Shelton, L. (Box 33)
    - Smith, Gerry (Box 33)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Parker (Box 33)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Z. (Box 33)
    - Swift, Wesley A. (Box 33)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 33)
    - Tanner Opal M. (Box 33)
    - Tulsa meeting (Box 33)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 33)
    - U. S. Senate Foreign Relations (Box 33)
      (GLKS testimony)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 33)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 33)
    - Washington letters (Box 33)
    - Waybright, Edgar (Box 33)
    - Wills (Box 33)
    - World Government (Box 33)
    - World Nationalist News Service (Box 33)
    - Worrell, Margaret (Box 33)
    - Xavier, Peter L. (Box 33)
    - Z (miscellaneous) (Box 33)
  - 1951
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 33)
    - Advertising (Box 33)
    - Antiques (Box 33)
    - Appeal letters (Box 33)
    - Armstrong, George W. (Box 33)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 33)
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 33)
    - Blake, Aldrich (Box 33)
    - Blank, Mrs. Helen (Box 33)
    - Britton, Frank (Box 34)
    - Burke, Emory (Box 34)
    - Burman, Paul (Box 34)
    - Ca-Cl (miscellaneous) (Box 34)
    - Cm-Cz (miscellaneous) (Box 34)
    - Cawthorn, Joe (Box 34)
    - Chicago trial (Box 34)
    - Christian Nationalist Party (Box 34)
    - Christian Publishers (Box 34)
    - Commercial Publishers (Box 34)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 34)
    - Davis, Phil W., Jr. (attorney) (Box 34)
    - Dilling case. (Box 34)
      (See also Davis, Phil W.)
    - Dog data (Box 34)
    - Doman, B. A. (Box 34)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 34)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 34)
    - Foreign letters (Box 34)
    - Freedman, Ben H. (Box 34)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 34)
    - Gostick, Ron (Box 34)
    - Green, G. F. (Box 34)
    - Ha-Hn (miscellaneous) (Box 34)
    - Ho-Hz (miscellaneous) (Box 34)
    - Kister, Frederick (Box 34)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 34)
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 34)
    - Lohbeck, Don - clippings (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 35)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 35)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 35)
    - MacArthur, Douglas (miscellaneous) (Box 35)
    - McCarthy, Joseph (Box 35)
    - McGinley, Conde (Box 35)
    - Manney Printing Co. (Box 35)
    - Memos, 6 folders (Box 35)
    - N (Box 35)
      (The Letters)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 35)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 35)
    - Operatives (Box 35)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 35)
    - Perkins, Jonathan E. (Box 35)
    - Petitions (blank) (Box 35)
    - Pollock, Clara (Box 35)
    - Robertson, Charles (Box 35)
    - Sa-Sh (miscellaneous) (Box 35)
    - Si-So (miscellaneous) (Box 35)
    - Sp-Sz (miscellaneous) (Box 35)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 35)
    - St. Louis meetings (Box 35)
    - Security National Bank, St. Louis (Box 35)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Z. (Box 36)
    - Special form letters (Box 36)
    - Tanner, O. M. (Box 36)
    - Tulsa (Box 36)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - Washington Letter (Box 36)
    - Wickenburg, Arizona (Box 36)
    - Y (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - Z (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
  - 1952
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - Advertising newspaper clippings (Box 36)
    - Antiques (Box 36)
    - Appeal letters (Box 36)
    - Armstrong, George W. (Box 36)
      (includes Armstrong Foundation)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 36)
    - Beaty, John (Box 36)
    - Blake, Aldrich (Box 36)
    - Blank, Brs. Helen (Box 36)
    - Britton, Frank (Box 36)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - Cash and checks (Box 36)
    - Circulars (Box 36)
    - Clark, Rev. Max A. X. (Box 36)
    - Comparet, Bertrand (Box 36)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - Daily Bulletin - GLKS (Box 36)
    - Davis, Phil W., Jr. (Box 36)
    - Delling law suit (Box 36)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - Editors Confidential - draft of publication (Box 36)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, about (Box 36)
    - Embassy Auditorium, Los Angeles (Box 36)
    - Essig, Mrs. C. H. (Box 36)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 36)
    - Fagan, Myron C. (Box 36)
    - Foreign letters (Box 36)
    - Frank, John (Box 36)
    - Fulton, Roger (Box 36)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 37)
    - Green, G. F. (Box 37)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 37)
    - Hamilton, John W. (Box 37)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 37)
    - International Advertising Agency (Box 37)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 37)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 37)
    - Kamp, Joseph (Box 37)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 37)
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles meeting
      - Announcements (Box 37)
      - Premiums (Box 37)
      - Printing (Box 37)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 37)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 37)
    - MacArthur, Douglas
      - Correspondence December 1951-August 1952 (Box 37)
      - Correspondence September-October 1952 (Box 37)
      - Correspondence, largely responses to mailings, 5 folders (Box 37)
      - MacArthur-Tenney Club
        - Financial records, reports to Congress (Box 37)
      - Christian Nationalist Party efforts
        - Tenney, Jack B. speeches (Box 37)
        - California ballot (Box 37)
        - Washington ballot (Box 37)
        - Other state's ballots (Box 37)
        - Campaign materials, 2 folders (Box 37)
        - Campaign music (Box 37)
        - Clippings, 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Miscellanea (Box 37)
    - McCarren Committee (Box 37)
    - McGinley, Conde (Box 37)
    - Manney, E. E. (Box 38)
      (Wichita Publishing Co.)
    - Matthews, Tandy (Box 38)
      (income tax)
    - Memos, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Methodist Quadrennial Conference (Box 38)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 38)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - Radio (Box 38)
    - Republican National Convention, Chicago (Box 38)
    - Reilly, Lawrence (Box 38)
    - Robertson, Mrs. B. N. (Box 38)
    - Robertson, B. N., Printing Co. (Box 38)
    - Robertson, Charles, Printing Co. (Box 38)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 38)
    - Samples (Box 38)
    - San Diego (Box 38)
    - San Francisco - Oakland meetings (Box 38)
    - Seattle Group (Box 38)
    - Smith, Earl (Box 38)
    - Smith, Gerald L. K. (Box 38)
      (introspective letter to family and staff)
    - Smith, Gerry (Box 38)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Z. (Box 38)
    - Sorenson, Mrs. S. C. (Box 38)
    - Stodghill, Tom (Box 38)
    - Swift, Wesley (Box 38)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - Tanner, Opal M. (Box 38)
    - Tenney, Jack B. (Box 38)
    - Tulsa (Box 38)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - Washington Letter (Box 38)
    - Washington State (Box 38)
    - Waybright, Edgar W. (Box 38)
    - Worrell, Margaret Hopkins (Box 38)
    - X-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
  - 1953
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - Advertising (Box 38)
    - Appeal letters (Box 38)
    - Ba-Bo (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
    - Bp-Bz (miscellaneous) (Box 38)
  - 1953
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 39)
    - Beaty, John (Box 39)
    - Ca-Co (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - Cp-Cz (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - Christian Nationalist Crusade
      - Reorganization (Box 39)
      - West Coast Convention, Oct. 20-21 (Box 39)
    - Circulars (Box 39)
    - Comparet, Bertrand (Box 39)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - Davis, Phil W., Jr. (Box 39)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - Essig, Edith (Box 39)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - Foreign letters (Box 39)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - Ha-Hd (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - He-Hz (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - Laughlin, James J. (Box 39)
    - Libel (Box 39)
    - Lohbeck, Donald (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 39)
      (largely circulars)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 39)
    - McCarran Act mailings (Box 39)
  - 1953
    - Mannery Printing Co. (Box 40)
    - Memos
      - Jan.-Mar. (Box 40)
      - Apr.-July: Tulsa (Box 40)
      - July-Dec. (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 40)
    - Myers, Jeretta B. (Box 40)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 40)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - Orders (Box 40)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - Q (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - Robertson, Charles (Box 40)
    - Robertson, Charles: printing orders (Box 40)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 40)
    - San Francisco Conference (Box 40)
      (to abolish United Nations)
    - Smith, Mrs. L. Z. (Box 40)
    - Special letters - responses to gifts of money (Box 40)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - Tenney, Jack (Box 40)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
    - Washington Letters (Box 40)
    - Wichita Publishing Co. (Box 40)
    - Wood, John T. (Box 40)
      (Idaho congressman)
    - Worrell, Margaret Hopkins (Box 40)
    - Y-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 40)
  - 1954 (Box 41)
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 41)
    - Allison, Willis (Box 41)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 41)
    - Andrew, Willedd (Box 41)
    - Appeal letters (Box 41)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 41)
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 41)
    - Beaty, John (Box 41)
    - Blank, Mrs. Helen (Box 41)
    - Bricker for President Club (Box 41)
    - Britton, Frank L. (Box 41)
    - Buckley, William, Jr. (Box 41)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 41)
    - Circulars (Box 41)
    - Clarke, Harry (Box 41)
    - Comparet, B. L. (Box 41)
    - Congressional Committee for the Investigation of Un-American Activities (Box 41)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 41)
    - Davis, Phil W., Jr. (Box 41)
    - Deatherage, George (Box 41)
    - Dilling, Elizabeth. See also Comparet and St. George files (Box 41)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 41)
    - Essig, Edith - manuscripts (Box 41)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 41)
    - Fagan, Myron (Box 41)
    - Foreign letters (Box 41)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 41)
    - Genocide Convention (Box 41)
    - Gostick, Ron (Box 42)
    - Ha-Hi (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - Hj-Hz (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - Herald Express, Los Angeles article, Jan. 9 (Box 42)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - Laughlin, James L. (Box 42)
  - 1954
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles meetings (Box 42)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 42)
    - MacArthur, Douglas (Box 42)
    - McCarthy, Joseph (Box 42)